http://www.inspired.co.nz/privacy-policy

Book Appointment
Home/Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We value your privacy! We will never give, lease, sell or otherwise disclose your personal information. Any information you give to Inspired will be held with the utmost care.
A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions at all about our privacy policy, please email us.
Resale or Disclosure of Information to Third Parties
Inspired does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected by our website, including contact forms, download requests or email lists.
Usage Information Collected By Our Website
Inspired does collect information about how people are using our website in order to improve the value of our website and the materials available on the web site.
Privacy of our Email Lists
Individuals join our mailing lists and are added to our email database using the forms provided on this web site.
We do not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease the addresses on our lists to anyone.
In addition, we configure our email software to refuse to divulge the email addresses of our list subscribers to anyone but authorised Inspired staff, including other list subscribers.
Unsubscribe Policy
We strive to only send e-mail to those who want to receive it. If you would not like to receive future e-mails from us, please use the 'unsubscribe' link located at the bottom of our email communications.
Stay Informed Sign up for expert investment ideas and financial news and
alerts.
Enter Email Address
Subscribe
Subscribe
Get inspired today with a free 30 minute no obligation chat about your business.
Book Appointment
